Hello.
We are from CLUB.
Thank you.
so, what is it for today?
Well, it's difficult, doesn't it?
It's cute show.
Hello, everyone
I'd like to introduce aיע however I want
Kawaii six
Wellhey
This kind of staff
Introduce this because it will soon be
shipped
Yeah
e
in
The hashtag is
Club Kanae
The best
This pen knife is
made by
Kanae
Look at this
It's like a review
I don't know what's going on
with
Tarekawa
There was also a grab
Hello
It's
really
pan
Is it ?
Take
it
outside
de
a
We have prepared a lot of them!
I'm 166cm tall.
Like this.
I'm cute, right?
I'm quite thin.
I'm X-AILER.
I'm 155cm tall.
It's a little bit hot.
I'm going to wear this.
What's wrong?
This is the hashtag, Kurako Kawaii
Kaksan Tour.
The inside of the hashtag is a crown.
It's a design that has a natural
feeling.
I'm wearing a T-shirt that I found at
the place where I'm going to tour.
I'm going to wear this color.
I'm going to wear this.
I'm going to wear this with my manager.
I think it's a good idea.
If you're a man, you can wear this.
I don't think so.
I'm going to wear this so that I don't
get a cold.
I have a size 2.
I bought 5 of the things I found at the
store.
Next, I'm going to wear this hashtag,
Kurako Kawaii Kaksan Tour.
I'm going to wear this.
I think I'm going to wear this for the
first time.
I'm going to wear this.
I think I can go to a bar.
I'm going to wear this finger.
This is a finger of the person who I'm
going to tour.
These are eyes of our members.
Eyes?
It's a donut.
I'm going to wear this.
Please subscribe to our channel and
follow us on Twitter!
I don't know.
Then, I'll let you decide.
Actually,
the manager and the members
have been
working on this.
That's right.
It's been a while.
Yes.
Ah!
I'm sorry.
Takara-chan is up glowing again.
Hahaha.
That's a everybody's power!
Yeah!
I'm glad to see you again.
This one is your favourite!
Welcome to the event America release the
BUSH double icon exhibition!
Krab islessly, come down with the
country.
So, for the backflip...
Go outside with me...
I'm Shiro from Hokkaido.
I'm Akane from Osaka.
I'm Ai from Chiba.
I'm pink.
I'm Murasaki from Sendai.
I'm Katoi from Sendai.
I'm Kuro from Sendai.
I'm Kawaii from Chiba.
I'm Hiroshima.
I'm cute and bright orange.
I'm Miyagi.
I'm red.
I don't know why, but I like this color.
I'm Tsundamachi.
I'm green.
I'm Hikawa.
I'm yellow.
I'm from Minato.
I went to a tour in the U.S.
I went to Ishikawa.
I'm getting more and more colors.
I'm happy.
Thank you.
This is a watermelon.
This is a white walnut.
I decided the name of the goods.
The first one is a zip-up hoodie.
You can buy 10 of them.
So, I bought 10 of them.
11?
I bought a small one.
This is S size.
It's 159cm.
It's perfect.
It's perfect for those who wear a hoodie
with a small size.
So, I recommend S size for those who
wear it with a small size.
I bought M size.
It's a little big.
Wait a minute.
My height is 166cm.
I think you can wear a round sleeve.
I think so, too.
I think it's good.
I think it's perfect for long sleeves.
It's a good fit for a city girl.
This is the end of the video.
I'm 163cm tall.
I'm a little bit short.
This is a big size.
The butt is hidden.
I'm 155cm tall.
It's a set of clothes.
I can wear a T-shirt and a t-shirt.
I think it's good for short pants and
skirts.
It's good for girls.
It's a good size for men, too.
It's a good size.
If you want to wear a tight fit, I
recommend this.
This is XXL.
It's big.
I'm so big that my arms are hidden.
It's a good size.
It's big.
It's pretty big.
It's good for men.
It's good for women who wear T-shirts.
This is a good size.
It's a good size.
This pink and light green and white are
a good match.
It's a good size.
I'm so big that my arms are hidden.
Please change the clothes.
Thank you.
We're going to have a lot of events from
September 2nd to December 10th.
If you've never been to a concert,
please come and see us.
We'll be performing from the morning to
the evening.
If you have friends in the area, please
come with us.
Let's do it together.
If you hang out at a concert, I think
we'll have a lot of people around here.
Please look at this.
I'm so big that my arms are hidden.
Please edit this part.
We're waiting for you.
I don't know about the club, but I've
been watching you on YouTube.
I'd like to tell you that I love idols.
I'm doing SNS from the summary section.
Please check it out and come see us.
Thank you.
We're fromis'up.
Bye.
See you.
Please subscribe to this channel!